A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. (RBI) (and successors) records FA480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- RBI Management and Investment Policy, 1941-1985; 6; 12.7 Cubic Feet 26 letter document boxes and 6 legal document boxes.
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Aviation and Related Activities - Background and Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Miscellaneous Company Memos, 1958 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    Re: long range planning, exposure, diversification.
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Status Report - Existing Ventures, 1958 (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Staff Meetings, 1947-1948, 1958-1959 (Box 252, Folder 6-7)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Standard Investments - General, 1947-1950 (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Project Cards, 1957-1959 (Box 253, Folder 1-3)
  - Rockefeller Family and Associates - RBI Contributions, 1947-1966 (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Family and Associates - RBI - Directors Meetings, 1946-1949 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Family and Associates - RBI - Investment Policy, 1947 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Family and Associates - RBI - Organization and Procedure, 1946-1961 (Box 254, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller Family and Associates - RBI - Participants, 1947-1951 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Board of Directors and Annual Meetings - Minutes, 1946-1948 (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Board of Directors and Annual Meetings - Minutes, 1946-1953 (Box 255, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Board of Directors and Annual Meetings - Minutes, 1953-1957 (Box 256, Folder 1-5)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Incorporated - Board of Directors and Annual Meetings - Minutes, 1958-1962 (Box 257, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous Investment Files - A-Z, 1955-1969 (Box 258, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous Investment Files - 1970-1972 - A-Z (Box 265, Folder 1-3)
  - Miscellaneous Proposals - 1973 - A-Z (Box 258, Folder 3-4)
  - Miscellaneous Proposals - 1974 - A-Z (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Investment Files - 1975-1976 - A-Z (Box 266, Folder 1-4, Box 269, Folder 1)
  - Acme Industrial Supply Company, 1951-1955 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - Air Shopping Service Corp., 1952-1957 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Automatic Theater Company, 1946 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Avion Instrument Corporation, 1951-1952 (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Belgian Tin Mine Project, 1947-1951 (Box 259, Folder 5)
  - Burnelli, Vincent, 1946-1958 (Box 259, Folder 6)
  - Central Airlines, Inc., 1951-1964 (Box 259, Folder 7)
  - Pierre Cheyne, Inc. - General Correspondence, 1946-1959 (Box 259, Folder 8)
  - 834 Fifth Avenue, 1948-1956 (Box 259, Folder 9)
  - Hiline Transportation Company, 1948-1953 (Box 259, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Lease Holders, 1951 (Box 259, Folder 11)
  - Societe des Accumukteurs Fixes et de Traction (SAFT), 1953 (Box 259, Folder 12)
  - SASCHA Brastoff, Inc., 1948-1951 (Box 260, Folder 1-3)
    Includes correspondence, Winthrop Rockefeller interests and loans, and American Ceramics Products, Inc.
  - Institutional Venture Associates, 1973 (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - Emerald Coal and Coke Company, 1941-1961 (Box 261, Folder 1-2)
  - Vibrane - Correspondence, 1952-1969 (Box 260, Folder 5-8, Box 261, Folder 3-6, Box 262, Folder 1-2)
  - Vibrane - Agreements, 1958-1966 (Box 262, Folder 3-5)
  - Vibrane - Patents, 1953-1965 (Box 262, Folder 6, Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Vibrane - Dissolution, 1961-1963 (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Yukon Syndicate, 1952-1954 (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. - Reports to Directors - David Rockefeller Copies, 1948-1951 (Box 263, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. - Reports to Directors - David Rockefeller Copies, 1951-1960 (Box 264, Folder 1-4)
  - Hills Realty Company - Meeting Minutes, 1951-1972 (Box 267, Folder 1-4, Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Hills Realty Company - The Carlyle Corporation and Hills Realty Company - Exchange and Lease of Properties, 1965 April 26 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Selected Risk Investments (SRI) - Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 494, Folder 1-5)
  - Selected Risk Investments (SRI) - Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 495, Folder 1-7)
  - Selected Risk Investments (SRI) - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 493, Folder 2)
  - Venrock Associates - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 493, Folder 3-4)
    Custodial History
    Received from Ray Neugebauer
  - Venrock Associates - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 496, Folder 1-3)
  - Venrock Associates - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 497, Folder 1-4)
  - Venrock Associates - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 498, Folder 1-5)
  - Venrock Associates - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 499, Folder 1-4)
  - Venrock Associates - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 500, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Thrift Plan Trust (RBTPT), 1969-1980 (Box 501, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Thrift Plan Trust (RBTPT) - Financial Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 501, Folder 3-4)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Thrift Plan Trust (RBTPT) - Meetings, 1975-1980 (Box 502, Folder 1-3)
  - William Kelly Simpson, 1980-1985 (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - William Kelly Simpson - Ovation Enterprises, 1977 (Box 500, Folder 4)
  - William Kelly Simpson - Entertainment Capital Corp. - Shareholders, 1977-1981 (Box 500, Folder 5)
  - William Kelly Simpson - Entertainment Capital Corp., 1977-1978 (Box 503, Folder 1-2)
  - William Kelly Simpson - Entertainment Capital Corp., 1979-1984 (Box 500, Folder 6)
  - William Kelly Simpson - Tangiers Productions, 1977-1983 (Box 502, Folder 4-6)